这是
It's...
蒙提·派森的恶搞之家
Monty Python's Family Guy
片头向"蒙提·派森的飞行马戏团"(Monty Python's Flying Circus)致敬
BBC 70年代的一档小品电视节目
太空军校生
Space Cadet
本集剧情类似美国1986年电影"太空险航"(Space Camp)
Chris 你读一下自己的个人作文好吗
Chris, would you like to read your personal essay?
好的 Donovan夫人
Okay, Mrs. Donovan.
"尾行Donovan夫人" 作者 Chris Griffin
"Following Mrs. Donovan" by Chris Griffin.
"Donovan下班回家后干的
"The first thing that Mrs. Donovan does
第一件事就是换上运动裤
"when she gets home from school is put on sweatpants.
然后她会吃掉一整筒曲奇饼
"Then she eats a whole tube of cookie dough,
但她一定对它过敏
"but she must be allergic to it
因为眼泪从她眼中涌出
"because there are tears coming out of her eyes
而且她总是吃完就呕吐
"and she always throws up right after.
然后她把纸娃娃的衣服
"Then she puts paper doll clothes
穿在一张B超图上"
on a picture of a sonogram."
Chris 我想你该停下了
Chris, I think you should stop.
什么 我已经尽力了啊
What? I'm doing the best I can.
我又不是纳撒尼尔·霍桑
I'm not Nathaniel Hawthorne.
美国作家1804-1864 代表作《红字》等
纳撒尼尔 你干嘛呢
Nathaniel, what are you doing?
正在毁掉所有人的九年级而已
Just ruining ninth grade for everyone.
Griffin夫妇 我今天叫你们来
Mr. and Mrs. Griffin, I called you in today
是因为你们儿子Chris最近
because your son, Chris, has been getting
惹了不少的麻烦
in quite a bit of trouble lately.
事实上 就在昨天 他试图
In fact, just yesterday, he tried to pass
用这幅画来冒充他的高级美术课作业
this drawing off as his Advanced Art project.
Fox的另一档动画"开心汉堡店"(Bob's Burgers)
- 天啊 - 我感觉非常尴尬
- Oh, my. - I'm very embarrassed.
有些人是该如此
Well, someone should be.
我很抱歉Shepherd校长
I'm sorry, Principal Shepherd.
我们以前也试过跟他谈话
We've tried talking to Chris.
只是不知道还能做什么了
We just don't know what else to do.
我想我们也许有个解决办法
Well, I think we may have a solution.
我们学校附近有不少流浪猫
We have these cats that hang around the school,
我们会喂它们
and we feed them.
为何不让Chris也加入它们
Why doesn't Chris come in,
这样我们就能像流浪猫一样对待他了
and we can treat him like one of the cats?
这样几年后 我们会给他发个文凭
And in a couple of years, we'll give him a diploma.
这样听起来不像
That doesn't sound like
他会得到最好的教育
he'll be getting the best education.
我不知道 Lois
I don't know, Lois.
那些猫有不少找到很好的工作了
Some of those cats go on to get pretty good jobs.
- 喵 - 是我
- meow - Yep.
继续播放"绝命毒师"
ANNOUNCER: We now return to Breaking Bad.
AMC的一档剧情类电视剧(2008- )
你会向你认识的所有人推荐"绝命毒师"
You will recommend Breaking Bad to everyone you know.
我会向我认识的所有人推荐"绝命毒师"
I will recommend Breaking Bad to everyone I know.
"绝命毒师"是你迄今看过最好的电视剧
Breaking Bad is the best show you've ever seen,
也许除了"火线"之外
except maybe The Wire.
HBO的一部剧情类电视剧(2002-2008)
"绝命毒师"是我迄今看过最好的电视剧
Breaking Bad is the best show I've ever seen,
也许除了"火线"之外
except maybe The Wire.
你会滔滔不绝的谈论
You will never stop talking
"绝命毒师"或者"火线"
about Breaking Bad or The Wire.
我会滔滔不绝的谈论"绝命毒师"或者"火线"
I will never stop talking about Breaking Bad or The Wire.
Peter 我真的很担心Chris
Peter, I'm really worried about Chris.
我们该拿他怎么办
What are we going to do about him?
面对现实吧 那孩子是个白痴
Let's face it, the kid is an idiot.
我们家的聪明基因都他妈怎么了
What the hell happened to all the smart genes in this family?
我是说 我发明了刀片梳
I mean, I invent the razor blade comb,
但我的孩子却一事无成
and my kids are doing nothing.
我是说 当Chris长大后 他能够
I mean, when Chris grows up, will he even be able
找到工作或照顾自己么
to get a job or take care of himself?
还有当我们死了后他要怎么办
And what's he going to do when we die?
Ooga chaka, ooga ooga, ooga chaka...
Hooked on a Feeling
我停不下这感觉
I can't stop this feeling
它在我内心深处
Deep inside of me...
我讨厌这么说
I feel awful saying it,
但我有时候会被他弄得很尴尬
but I'm kind of embarrassed by him sometimes.
我知道 而且他也有胸部
I know, and he's got boobs, too.
有胸部的傻子
Stupid guy with boobs.
表现得好像他不想我们看一样
Acting like he doesn't want us to look.
但他就想让我们看到
He wants us to look.
不准取笑我了
CHRIS: Stop making fun of me!
我只想偷听你们嘿咻
I just wanted to listen to you guys have sex,
但你们却在说我的坏话
but you were saying mean things about me.
Chris 上帝啊
Chris! Oh, my God.
不是 我们没在说你
No, we weren't talking about you.
是啊 我们在说Meg
Yeah, we were talking about Meg.
我们叫她Chris 这样她就不知道了
We call her Chris so she doesn't know.
- **你们 - 闭嘴 Chris
MEG: (bleep) you! - Shut up, Chris!
我知道你们在骗人
I know that's not true.
天啊
Oh, God.
Peter 他听见我们说他傻了
Peter, he heard us call him stupid.
他自己的父母
His own parents.
我们都做了什么啊
What have we done?
其实你知道 Lois
Well, you know, Lois,
听到真相从来都不是件容易事
it's never easy hearing the truth.
尤其是从幸运饼干中
Especially from a fortune cookie.
[你老婆正打算离开你]
上面怎么说 Peter
What does it say, Peter?
呃 就是些讲坚持不懈的
Uh, just something about perseverance.
你的上面怎么说
What does yours say?
上面说我非常有创意
It says I'm very creative.
[他知道了 你应该现在就行动]
哦对了 我学前班里有个带HIV的婴儿
Oh, by the way, there's a baby in my preschool with HIV,
我老师给你些文件要签名
and my teacher gave you something to sign
好把他赶出去
to get him kicked out.
嘿 Chris
Hey, Chris!
我魁梧聪明的儿子
There's my big, smart son.
我的真命天子 我的Chrissy
My special guy, my Chrissy.
听起来有人把她的按摩棒修好了
Sounds like someone got her vibrator working again.
噢 各位当心了
Oh, look out, everyone.
IQ两位数的人要来吃饭了
Double-digit IQ joining the table.
- 嘿 小聪明 转动你的脑子 - 啊
- Hey, smarty, think fast. - Aah!
他懂了 他明白那很烫了
He knows. He knows it's hot.
因为他很聪明
'Cause he's smart.
我不想和你们说话
I don't want to talk to you guys.
你们叫我白痴
You called me an idiot.
哦 Chris 你一定是听错了
Oh, Chris, you must have just misheard us.
我当时就站在那儿
I was standing right there.
怎么可能听错
How is that possible?
因为你是个白痴 这就是原因
'Cause you're an idiot-- that's how.
Peter!
我去上学了
I'm going to school!
今天是周日 对吧
It's Sunday, right?
Peter 我们已经彻底毁掉他的自尊了
Peter, we've completely destroyed his self-esteem.
我们得做点什么
We've got to do something.
你知道 Lois 如果Chris有自信心的问题
You know, Lois, if Chris is having confidence issues,
有针对他这种孩子的训练营
they have camps for kids like him.
怎么说
What do you mean?
他们接收在学校难以度日的孩子
Well, they take kids who struggle in school
帮助他们在关怀的环境中重拾自信
and help them gain self-confidence in a nurturing environment.
哇 这真是个好主意
Wow. That's actually a great idea.
我们没有钱给他参加训练营
We don't got no money for camp.
我们要存钱去欧洲呢
We're saving up to go to Europe.
Peter 我们去过欧洲 你不喜欢
Peter, we went to Europe. You didn't like it.
天啊 真美
Oh, my God, it's beautiful.
我的电视不在这儿 我们回家吧
My TV isn't here. Let's go home.
现在继续播放"加拿大恐怖故事"
ANNOUNCER: We now return to Canadian Horror Story.
恶搞FX台的"美国恐怖故事"(American Horror Story)
嘿 亲爱的 我们没有Molson了
Hey, hon, we're out of Molson.
噢 别担心
Oh, not to worry.
我们还有些Labatt在车库里
We've got some Labatt's in the garage.
你能给鬼拿一份么
And could you get one for the ghost?
不要
Boo, eh?
嘿 Chris 我们能和你谈谈吗
Hey, Chris, could we talk to you?
如果你们想再羞辱我一次 那就走开吧
If you're going to insult me again, just go away.
听着 甜心 我们很抱歉
Look, honey, we're sorry,
我们想为你做些特别的事
and we want to do something special for you.
这是台咸美顿牌搅拌器
This is a Hamilton Beach blender
我们在婚礼时收到的
we got on our wedding day.
它不停地回到我们手中
It keeps coming back to us
是一个礼物转送的恶性循环
in a vicious regifting cycle.
不 Peter
No, Peter.
Chris 我们想送你去训练营
Chris, we were thinking of sending you to camp.
我们想让你自己选一个
And we're going to let you choose which one.
这个叫头盔营
This one's called Camp Helmet.
这个叫坐下不动营
This one's called Camp Sit 'N' Stay.
这些训练营听着都很无聊
These camps don't sound fun at all.
Chris 其实训练营(集中营)有不有趣是看你自己
Well, Chris, camp is only as fun as you make it.
在第二次世界大战中就是如此
That's how it was in World War II.
我不觉得这会有什么帮助
Don't suppose it would help
如果我说我有医生开的条子
to say I have a note from my doctor.
进去 你
Get in there, you.
嘿 这个看上去挺酷的
Hey, this one looks cool.
太空营
Space Camp.
"花费一周进行紧张的数学与科学训练
"Spend a week doing intensive math and science,
学习如何成为一位真正的宇航员"
learning from real astronauts."
太空营
Space Camp?
我很抱歉 那个一定是
I'm sorry, that one must have
不小心混进来的
accidentally gotten in with the rest of them.
你们在说什么 我太笨了不适合太空营么
What are you saying? That I'm too stupid for it?
Chris 我们在这边
Chris, we're over here.
你们在说什么
What are you saying?
是因为我太笨了吗
That I'm too stupid for it?
不 不 绝对不是
No, no, of course not.
那我就选这个了
Then this is the camp I choose.
吔 我要去太空营了
Yay! I get to go to Space Camp!
谢谢妈跟爸
Thanks, Mom and Dad.
你们是有史以来最棒的父母了
You guys are the best parents ever!
可以失陪一下么
Would you excuse me a moment?
现在它们是我的了
These are mine now.
嘿
Hey!
噢 亲爱的 当我们接受这些马克杯时
Oh, honey, when we accepted those mugs,
我们就知道会有这样一天的
we knew this could happen.
[肯尼迪航空中心 佛罗里达卡纳维拉尔角]
知道么 Chris 现在改变
You know, Chris, it's not too late
去太空营的主意还不晚
to change your mind about Space Camp.
有时候想要融入到
Sometimes it can be tough to fit in
新的一群人中是很难的
with a new group of people.
没错 当我"深入了解"童子军后
Yeah, I sure had my troubles
发现确实是挺麻烦的
when I got involved with the Boy Scouts.
营员们从没有
At no time were the campers
和Griffin先生同时裸体
and Mr. Griffin naked simultaneously.
他们只是闹着玩而已
They merely engaged in horseplay.
Griffin先生有鸡奸孩子们么
Did Mr. Griffin sodomize the boys?
Griffin先生坚决否认所有指控
Mr. Griffin vehemently denies all allegations.
妈 我搞得定太空营
Mom, I can handle Space Camp.
我不笨
I'm not stupid.
那你不管如何 在回去的路上
Well, regardless, on the way back,
我们会在路过的唐氏综合症营停车
we're stopping at that Down syndrome camp we passed.
Peter 那是佛罗里达大学
Peter, that was the University of Florida.
欢迎来到太空营
Welcome to Space Camp.
[太空营登记处]
嗨 我们来给我们儿子Chris Griffin登记
Hi. We're here to register our son, Chris Griffin.
噢 很高兴见到你 Chris
Oh, great to meet you, Chris.
嘿 这孩子就是我的全部
Hey, this kid means the world to me.
看好他 好么
Keep an eye on him, huh?
嘿 那是什么 我以为全部
Hey, what's that? I thought all
航天飞机都退役了
the space shuttles were decommissioned.
其实 我们总是保持一部宇宙飞船做好起飞准备
Well, we always keep one spacecraft flight-ready
以备卫星需要服务
in the event a satellite needs service,
太空站的紧急情况
there's a space station emergency
或者一个意大利佬要吹吹牛逼
or an Italian guy needs to overexaggerate.
我发誓 Johnny 我已经受够...
I swear to God, Johnny, I've had it up to...
...你的屁话到这里了
...here with your BS.
噢 他这次是真的做到了
Ooh, he's really had it this time.
抱歉 Louie
I'm sorry, Louie!
那么好吧
All right, then.
嘿 那里面是什么
Hey, what's that in there?
那是感官剥夺室
That's a sensory deprivation room
让我们的宇航员
that prepares our astronauts
为恐怖的太空空虚感做好准备
for the terrifying emptiness of space.
噢 酷
Oh, cool.
嘿 来吧 Brian 和我试试
Hey, come on, Brian, try it with me.
事情变得疯狂的太快了
Things got crazy so fast.
再见 Chris 祝你好运
Bye, Chris. Good luck.
保重 Chris
Take care, Chris.
哦 对了 如果你被送去执行太空任务
Oh, and hey, if you get sent off on a space mission,
呃 不要做那个黑人 否则你会死的
um, don't be the black guy, 'cause you'll die.
我知道你会玩的很开心
I know you're going to have fun
然后交到很多好朋友的
and make lots of good friends.
没错 而且是真朋友
Yeah, and not fake friends,
就像妻子也是朋友的人
like guys whose wives are friends.
你得告诉我那个菜谱
You have to get me that recipe.
天啊 烹饪书么
Oh, my God, the cookbook?
就在厨房里呢
It's right in the kitchen.
- 运动? - 不
- Sports? - No.
- 电影? - 不
- Movies? - No.
- 远足? - 不
- Hiking? - No.
- 车? - 不
- Cars? - No.
- 毛片? - 毛片?
- Porn? - Porn?
- 没错 - 没错
- Yes! - Yes!
- 同志毛片? - 不
- Gay porn? - No.
欢迎到太空营来 各位
Welcome to Space Camp, everyone.
一定要拿好你们的物理课本
Be sure to grab your physics textbooks.
你们也许想温习下
And you may want to brush up
明天关于轨道动力学讲座的内容
for tomorrow's lecture on orbital dynamics.
天啊 我不属于这儿 而且他们知道
Oh, man. I don't belong here, and they know it.
人们总能发现那个滥竽充数的
People can always sense a fraud.
先生们 我注意到
Gentlemen, it has come to my attention
这里面有一个中国人
that there's a Chinese among us.
放心 我们会找到他的
Rest assured, he will be found.
保安已经开展了对我们每位
Security is launching a full-scale investigation
员工家谱的全面调查
into the genealogy records of every single one of our employees.
我们会找到他的
This man will be found,
否则后果不堪设想
and there will be dire consequences.
那个中国人麻烦大了吧
Too bad about that Chinese guy, huh?
营员们 我们现在在
Campers, we are now in
我们的最先进的航天飞机模拟器中
our state-of-the-art space shuttle simulator.
嘿 你是个妹子 我刚发现的
Hey, you're a girl. I just figured that out.
当你离开太空营时
By the time you leave Space Camp,
你们都会熟悉
you will all be familiar
这艘飞船上的所有设备
with every device on board this craft.
这个按钮是干嘛的
What's this button do?
你干嘛不按下去试试
Why don't you go ahead and push it?
这是我的乐队
That's my band.
[太空营训练中心]
好了 营员们 瞧瞧你们的宇航员发型
Okay, campers, let's see your astronaut haircuts.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
嗯 嗯
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Chris 那是个拉塞尔布兰德的发型
Chris, that's a Russell Brand haircut.
英国喜剧演员 歌手 作家
哦 我不知道怎么回事
Oy, I don't know what happened.
我去了我的理发店
I went to me barber at the shop,
我出来后就成了这个样子
and I come out, I'm looking like this.
你和我讲话讲的不一样
You're talking different from how I talk.
你上电视话给你一大笔钱
Here's a bunch of money to be on TV.
如果你看过"阿波罗13号" 你们就知道他们得
If you all saw Apollo 13, you know they had to fix
用太空舱里仅有的工具修好空气洗涤器
an air scrubber with just the tools in the capsule.
Griffin 我要你用这些工具修复我的婚姻
Griffin, I need you to use these tools to fix my marriage.
我做不到
I can't do that.
那我不能是唯一努力的人啊
Well, I can't be the only one who's trying.
[男生宿舍]
喂
Hello?
天啊 Chris 怎么了
Oh, my God, Chris. What's wrong?
妈 我讨厌这里
Mom, I hate it here.
我想回家
I want to come home.
所有孩子都很坏
All the kids are mean,
而且我任何事都做不好
and I keep messing everything up.
就连机器人Jinx也捉弄我
Even Jinx the Robot is picking on me.
电影"太空险航"(Space Camp)中的角色
嘿 你衣服上有东西
Hey, you've got something on your shirt.
玩笑达成
Joke complete.
你和爸是对的
You and dad were right.
我太笨不适合这里
I'm not smart enough to be here.
你能来接我吗 求你了 妈
Can you come get me, please, Mom?
好的 宝贝 我们当然会接你的
Okay, honey, of course we will.
等下 有电话进来
Hang on, I got another call.
喂
Hello?
Lois 我在体育馆
Lois, I'm at the gym.
我讨厌这里
I hate it here.
我想回家
I want to come home.
所有人都很坏
Everybody's so mean.
还有一个人跟着我
And there's this one guy who follows me around
说我胖
and calls me fat.
呃 我想我...
Well, I suppose I...
等下 宝贝 又有电话进来
Hang on, honey, I'm getting another call.
喂
Hello?
嘿 死胖子回家了没
Hey, is fat ass home yet?
让他听 我想和他说话
Put him on, I want to talk to him.
谢谢你们来接我
Thanks for coming to get me, you guys.
嘿 没问题的
Hey, no problem.
我们花了上万元送你来这儿
We spent thousands of dollars to send you here
然后4天里来了两趟佛罗里达
and made two trips to Florida in four days.
我很高兴我们生了你
I'm glad we had you.
我很抱歉 我以为我能搞定这里的
Well, I'm sorry, I thought I could handle it here,
但我错了
but I was wrong.
没关系 宝贝 人人都会犯错
That's okay, honey, everyone makes mistakes.
是啊 还记得胖子带回家的那个熟女小妞么
Yeah, remember when the fat man brought home that cougar chick?
请随意 Beth
You make yourself comfortable, Beth.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
嘿 年轻人
Hi, young man.
我正想找乐子呢
I'm looking for a good time.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
我很老练 很有趣
I'm worldly. I'm fun.
这不是公共汽车 只是经验丰富
This ain't mileage, this is experience.
没兴趣
Not interested.
听着 就是告诉你不会有什么"惊喜"
Listen, just so there are no surprises,
别害怕- 我那东西看起来像
don't be scared-- my stuff looks like
有人在我腿间洒了个苹果派
someone spilled an apple pie in my lap.
恶心
Yuck.
你一点乐趣都没有么 甜心
Didn't you have any fun at all, sweetie?
呃 我倒是每天都上了那个航天飞机
Well, I guess I did get to go on the space shuttle everyday.
真的么 骗人的吧
Really? No way.
我一直想当个像兰斯·阿姆斯特朗一样的宇航员
I always wanted to be an astronaut like Lance Armstrong.
美自行车运动员
那是尼尔·阿姆斯特朗
It's Neil Armstrong.
他也用了假名么
He lied about his name, too?
哇 这太棒了 Chris
Wow, this is amazing, Chris.
看看这个 Lois
Look at this, Lois.
一周前 我们说他笨
a week ago, we call him stupid,
现在他却带我们参观太空飞船
and now he's giving tours of the space shuttle.
负强化 这才是关键
Negative reinforcement-- that's the key.
指在一个行为之后取消或减弱某种刺激 从而使某种行为出现的可能性增加
对不 笨蛋
Right, stupid?
噢 我会做得更好的
Ow! I'll do better.
那你知道这些东西如何运作么
So, do you know how all this stuff works?
那个 大部分按钮我不知道是干什么的
Well, I don't know what most of these buttons do,
但我知道这个红色大按钮是发射用的
but I know this big red one is the one you press to launch.
喔 红色大按钮
Whoo, big red button!
Stewie 不要
Stewie, no!
[发射程序启动]
啊哦
Uh-oh.
Chris 让它停下
Chris, make it stop.
我正在努力呢
I'm trying.
我想...我想我们发射了
I think... I think we're launching.
天啊 所有人系好自己
Oh, my God, everyone strap yourselves in.
Stewie 拉住我的手
Stewie, hold my hand.
不 谢了 我宁愿死于
No, thank you, I prefer to die
对你比中指
giving you the finger.
如果离开佛罗里达需要这样 那么好吧
If this is what it takes to get out of Florida, fine.
知道么 人生就只有这么一回
You know what, you only live once.
我要把头伸到窗外去
I am sticking my head out the window.
啊 这是这种娱乐能达到的最高境界了
Yes, this is the best version of whatever's so enjoyable about this.
妈 我好怕
Mom, I'm scared.
我不敢相信
I don't believe it.
我们真的被困在太空了么
Are we really stuck in space?
天啊 如果我们的余生都得
Oh, God, what if we have to live up here
住在这里该怎么办
for the rest of our lives?
我会想念在醉蚌喝酒的时光的
I'm gonna miss drinking at The Clam.
我来告诉你什么是我不会想念的
I'll tell you what I won't miss.
那个自己为自己很搞笑的侍者
That waiter who thinks he has to be funny.
是的 请给我来份总汇沙拉
Yes, I'd like the chopped salad, please,
还有可以不要给我放洋葱么
and could I get no onions on that?
嗯 我和厨房还是有点关系的
Hmm, I've got a few connections in the back.
我尽力而为吧
I'll see what I can do.
挺好笑的
Yeah, that's funny.
如果沙拉中有一片洋葱
If there's one onion on that salad,
你就别想要你赖以为生的1块8小费了
you can forget the $1.80 tip you need to live.
抱歉各位 都是我的错
I'm sorry, you guys, this is all my fault.
我不应该带你们上这宇宙飞船的
I never should've brought you on the space shuttle.
你们是对的-- 我是很笨
You were right-- I am stupid.
- 飞船上有人吗 - 喂
- Hello, up there. - Hello?
我知道你们现在一定都吓坏了
I know you all must be pretty terrified right now,
但我们正在尽一切努力
but we're doing everything in our power
来让你们安全的返回地球
to get you safely back to earth.
这个我们很在行 好比八次击球有六个安打
We're pretty good at this-- we're like six for eight.
指棒球的打击率
我们能做点什么吗
Is there anything we can do?
所幸飞船正在自动驾驶
Well, fortunately the ship runs on autopilot.
我们只需要点时间来查出你们的坐标
We just need some time to figure out your coordinates,
然后计算出重返地球计划
and calculate the reentry plan.
那么试着放轻松 我们会把一切都解决的
So, just try to stay calm and we'll figure this all out.
另外 你们现在都很火了
By the way, you're all quite famous now.
所有新闻频道都在播你们
You're on every news channel.
下午好 我是布莱恩·威廉姆斯
Good afternoon, I'm Brian Williams.
NBC新闻主播 由其本人配音
头条新闻 一架航天飞机意外发射
Our top story, an accidental space shuttle launch
把一个罗德岛家庭送入了轨道
that has sent a Rhode Island family into orbit.
欲知更多详情 我们现在连线到当地新闻频道
For more on the story, we go to our local affiliate
圆蛤市第五频道 现在Tom Tucker正在现场
Channel Five Quahog where Tom Tucker is on the scene.
Tom?
谢谢 Brian
Thanks, Brian.
我 呃 看到你打开了我的生日电子邀请函
I, uh, saw that you opened my birthday Evite.
Evite是一个创建 发送 管理邀请的网站
现在我只需要你继续点回复
Now I just need you to go ahead and reply.
我正站在Griffin家的房子前
I'm standing here at the home of the Griffin family,
和他们的邻居聊天
chatting with their neighbors.
那么 Griffin一家可能会死
So, the Griffins might be dead.
这样你有什么感觉
How does that make you feel?
Griffin死? 我要了
Griffin dead? I take.
不 不 他们可能会死
No, no, they might be dead.
他们也可能会继续活着
They also might still be alive.
没问题的 我要了
It's okay, I-I take.
Peter 你在干嘛
Peter, what are you doing?
我要去太空漫步一下 Lois
I'm going out for a space walk, Lois.
你知道 这是我们唯一的机会
You know, this is our one chance
来直接体验太空令人敬畏的奇妙之处
to experience the awe-inspiring wonders of space firsthand.
哇 酷毙了
Wow, neat.
原来这就是太空
So, this is space.
[体育新闻 坦帕湾 4 波士顿 3]
妈的
Damn it.
[醉酒女孩摔出购物车]
哈 傻逼醉酒贱货
Ha! Stupid drunk bitches.
嘿 Brian 看这个
Hey, Brian, check it out.
Meg正在货仓闲逛呢
Meg's poking around the cargo hold.
我来吓她一下
I'm gonna give her a little scare.
天啊 我想这太空食物已经坏了
Aw, boy, I think this space food has gone bad.
Peter 那是粪便收集袋
Peter, that's a fecal collection bag.
噢 还专门有个包啊
Oh, there's a bag for that?
因为我的正在那边的空中打转
'Cause mine's over there twirling in the air
像个缓慢的指挥棒一样
like a slow baton.
好吧 得有人来带领这支军乐队 呃
STEWIE: Well, someone's got to lead this marching band. Ew!
Griffin回话
MAN: Griffins come in.
是 是的 我们在
Yes! Yes, we're here.
我们有些好消息
Well, I have some good news.
自动驾驶可以带你们回家
The autopilot is capable of taking you home.
但是你们...
But guys...
...来启动 我们要...
...to engage, we're gonna...
...让飞船脱离...
...to take the shuttle out of...
喂?
Hello?
喂 日 我想我们联系不到他了
Hello? Crap, I think we lost him.
让我来修修看
Let me fix that.
如果电台DJ已经教会我电台的一切
If radio deejays have taught me anything about radio,
那你只需要干两件事
it's that you got to do two things.
打开然后把旋钮拔掉
Turn it up and rip the knob off.
Peter 不要
Peter, no!
妈的 这下我们完全失去联络了
Damn it, now we've lost communication entirely.
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
我不知道 但我们得试试各种方法
I don't know, but we got to try something.
如果我们不尽快让飞船脱离轨道
If we don't get this shuttle out of orbit soon,
我们将会耗尽氧气而亡
we're gonna run out of oxygen and die.
可以选则失败么
Is failure an option?
不行
No, it's not.
啊 那就是我的提议
Aw, that was my suggestion.
好了 来吧各位 我得集思广益
All right, come on, everyone, we got to put our heads
找到一个解决办法
together and try to find a solution.
别担心-- Griffin一家有解决难题的悠久历史
Don't worry-- Griffins have a long history of figuring stuff out.
就像我的曾祖父
Like my great-grandfather
他发明了首个情趣用品
who invented the first marital aid.
这给了我一个创意
This gives me an idea.
她死了
She's dead.
好了快点 如果指挥中心认为
All right, come on, if mission control thought
我们可以帮助飞船脱离轨道
we could help get the shuttle out of orbit,
这一定不难的
it can't be that hard.
好吧 好吧 呃 试试这个
Okay, okay, uh, try this.
按上上下下
Hit up, up, down, down,
左右左右BA 开始(魂斗罗)
left, right, left, right, B, A, start.
这样我们就有无限命了
Then we'll have unlimited lives.
拜托 我们要没时间了
Come on, we're running out of time.
噢 Meg 亏你这么多年来的自杀威胁
Oh, Meg, all your suicide threats over the years,
结果你还是和我们一样他妈的胆小
and you're just as chicken (bleep) as the rest of us.
各位 我想我有个能自救的办法
Hey, guys, I think I have an idea that could help us.
在太空营中 我们学习了用制动火箭来抵消前进动力
In Space Camp, we learned about countering forward momentum with retro rockets.
如果我们现在启动它们 飞船可能会减速到能让
If we use them now, the ship might slow down enough
重力把我们拉出轨道
for gravity to pull us out of orbit.
那个鸡蛋是我奉送给你成为书呆子的礼物
PETER: That's an egg that I hucked at you for being a nerd.
Chris 如果你觉得有用 那就试试看啊
Chris, if you think it'll help, just try it!
啊 我们正在减速 这是个好兆头
Ah, we're slowing down. That's a good sign.
你知道什么没有减慢么 "绝命毒师"
You know, what's not slowing down-- Breaking Bad.
自从"火线"后就没看过这么棒的剧
Haven't seen anything like it since The Wire.
天 他总是不停地讲那些电视剧
God, he never shuts up about those shows.
上帝啊
Oh, my God!
我想可能起作用了
I think it might be working!
飞船失控了
We're spinning out!
天啊 我们都要死了
MEG: Oh, my God, we're gonna die!
我还有那么多事没干过
There's so many things I didn't do.
我上不了大学了
I never got to go to college!
我的书没有全部放在我想放的地方
My book wasn't all I wanted it to be in spots!
Peter 我想和你一起变老
Peter, I wanted to grow old with you!
那个 你基本上这么做了
Well, you kind of did.
那件衣服我不能再穿得更好了
I never got to wear it better!
[红地毯 谁穿的更好看]
我得重新调整下制动火箭
I have to reorient the retro rockets
来抵消旋转
to counter the spin rotation!
Chris 你在干嘛
Chris, what are you doing?
救我们的命
Saving our lives.
啊 我希望他没那么说
Aw, I wish he hadn't said that.
现在我有点想给他喝倒彩了
Now I'm kind of rooting against him.
我们恢复正常了
We're straightening out!
啊 看 上面说"自动驾驶启动(订婚)"
Ah, look! It says "autopilot engaged."
为他高兴 我很高兴他找到了意中人
Good for him. I'm glad he found someone.
谢天谢地 我们得救了
Oh, thank God, we're saved!
我不敢相信我比德里克沃森先上太空
I can't believe I got to go to space before Derek Watson.
可能指的是一位现效力于卡加利牛仔队的橄榄球员
谁是德里克沃森
Who's Derek Watson?
现在可是小人物了
Nobody now.
他们返回大气层了
They've re-entered the atmosphere!
我不欢呼 我都不认识他们
I'm not cheering. I don't even know them.
那个 由于太空中没有重力
Well, thanks to no gravity in space,
我的脊柱拉伸了 我现在是个自信的六尺三寸(1.9米)的人
my spine stretched and I am now a confident six, three,
所以Lois 我要离开你找个更性感的女人
so, Lois, I will be leaving you for a hotter woman.
别介意 Lois 我非常爱你
Never mind, Lois, I love you so much.
[圆蛤消息报 本地英雄拯救生命并驾驶太空飞船着陆]
Chris 我们家现在还活着都是因为你
Chris, our family is alive right now because of you.
你救了我们
You saved us.
没错 伙计
That's right, buddy.
是你的智慧让我们度过了难关
It was your brains that pulled us through.
很抱歉我们怀疑过你
We're so sorry we ever doubted you.
谢谢你们
Thanks, you guys.
那还用说 小子
You bet, champ.
嘿对了 谁把我们家房子搬了
Hey, by the way, who moved our house?